<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Restify</string>

    <string name="bottom_nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_news">News</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_video">Video</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_model3d">3D</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_game">Game</string>

    <string name="home_greeting">Rest, chief!</string>
    <string name="home_sub_greeting">Hope your day\'s going well</string>
    <string name="home_game_on">Game on!</string>
    
    <string name="home_card_breaking_news">Breaking News</string>
    <string name="home_card_watch_videos">Watch Videos</string>
    <string name="home_card_3d_models">3D Model</string>
    <string name="home_card_games">Tic Tac Toe</string>

    <string name="terms_of_service_content">
        ⚠️ <b>IMPORTANT:</b>\n
        ⚠️ <b>EDUCATIONAL PROJECT DISCLAIMER ⚠️</b>\n
        <b>PLEASE READ THIS SECTION FIRST.</b>\n
        This application was developed solely as an assignment for the Mobile Application Development course at Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology.\n
        By accessing or reviewing this application, you acknowledge and agree to the following:\n
        <b>ACADEMIC PURPOSE ONLY:</b> This application is NOT a commercial product. It is a prototype created to demonstrate coding and design skills for grading purposes.\n
        <b>TEMPORARY EXISTENCE:</b> This project is ephemeral. All data, hosting, and access to this application will be permanently deleted upon the completion of the course.\n
        <b>PROHIBITION ON DISTRIBUTION:</b> You strictly may not copy, reproduce, distribute, or repurpose the design, logic, or assets of this application for any commercial or external use.\n
        <b>1. Content and Assets</b>\n
            All materials contained within this application, including but not limited to:\n
            - Illustrations and Graphics\n
            - Icons and Logos\n
            - Written Content\n
            - UI/UX Design Patterns\n
            Are utilized solely for the context of this specific course assignment.\n
            Ownership: Assets created by the developer remain the intellectual property of the student for grading purposes. Third-party assets (if any) are used under fair use for education.\n
            No Commercial Value: These assets serve no commercial function and must not be extracted or used elsewhere.\n
        <b>2. User Conduct</b>\n
            As this is a simulation, users (including graders and peer reviewers) agree:\n
            No Real Data: Do not enter real sensitive personal information (such as actual credit card numbers, real passwords, or private home addresses) into this application.\n
            No Expectation of Service: The developer guarantees no uptime, maintenance, or bug fixes beyond the scope of the assignment requirements.\n
        <b>3. Termination</b>\n
            The developer reserves the right to take down this application and delete the associated repository/database immediately after the assignment grade is finalized. No backups will be provided to users.\n
    </string>
</resources>